http://www.therai.org.uk/privacy-policy

HomeAbout the RAIOrder from usHistory & MissionGovernanceEthical PolicyStaffAnnual ReportGetting InvolvedRAI AnnouncementsCopyright and Terms of UseSite mapJobs & OpportunitiesVacanciesVisiting ScholarsJoiningTypes of AffiliationPricesApplication FormLinksContact UsSearch
Anthropological Index OnlineAnthropology LibraryArchives & ManuscriptsAwardsConferencesCommitteesDirectory of FellowsEvents CalendarEducationFilmForensic AnthropologyPhotographsPublicationsRoom HirePrivacy PolicySupport UsRAI Mailing List
Next event
Reviewer meets Reviewed: Being Bedouin Around Petra 19 Jan 2021;
04:00PM - 06:00PM
Book Launch: The Nuaulu world of plants & Nature Wars (Roy Ellen) 28 Jan 2021;
03:00PM - 05:00PM
RAI Research Webinar: Trevor Marchand 04 Feb 2021;
03:00PM - 05:00PM
Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice for Royal Anthropological Institute
This will be updated from time to time as appropriate.
List of articles in category Privacy Policy
Title
What personal data does the RAI collect, and what is it used for?
Who is your data shared with?
Where does this data come from?
How is your data stored?
Who is responsible for ensuring compliance with the relevant laws and regulations?
Who has access to your data?
What is the legal basis for collecting this data?
How you can check what data we have about you?
Does the RAI collect any “special” data?
How can you ask for data to be removed, limited or corrected?
How long we keep your data for, and why?
What happens if a member dies?
We use cookies on our website. Some of them are essential for the operation of the site, while others help us to improve this site and the user experience (tracking cookies). You can decide for yourself whether you want to allow cookies or not. Please note that if you reject them, you may not be able to use all the functionalities of the site.
Ok
